export const questionsNewest = [
  {
    id: 0,
    author: "Nweke Chidi",
    img: "Nweke Chidi",
    userName: "Chigoddy",
    question: "Fetch data using axios is so different from using fetch",
    tags: ["html", "css"],
    views: 5,
    answers: 0,
    timeAsked: 2,
    isAnswered: false,
  },

  {
    id: 1,
    author: "Bolanle Duke",
    img: "Bolanle Duke",
    userName: "Brandy",
    question:
      "How To Align Text Vertically Center Beside An Image In React Native With Code or can it be done any other way i really want you to help me out",
    tags: ["React", "Javascript"],
    views: 50,
    answers: 13,
    timeAsked: 5,
    isAnswered: true,
  },

  {
    id: 2,
    author: "Michael Binuyo",
    img: "Michael Binuyo",
    userName: "Mickkystonz",
    question:
      "How to validate email using regex in javascript, s this trully possible",
    tags: ["regex", "python"],
    views: 38,
    answers: 0,
    timeAsked: 5,
    isAnswered: false,
  },

  {
    id: 3,
    author: "Temitope Hamzat",
    img: "Temitope Hamzat",
    userName: "CodeT",
    question:
      "What is a potential pitfall with using typeof bar === 'object' to determine if bar is an object? How can this pitfall be avoided?",
    tags: ["html", "Javascript"],
    views: 13,
    answers: 10,
    timeAsked: 12,
    isAnswered: true,
  },

  {
    id: 4,
    author: "Adaeze Ndupu",
    img: "Adaeze Ndupu",
    userName: "Vermilion",
    question:
      "What is the significance, and what are the benefits, of including 'use strict' at the beginning of a JavaScript source file?",
    tags: ["Vue", "Javascript"],
    views: 50,
    answers: 13,
    timeAsked: 14,
    isAnswered: true,
  },

  {
    id: 5,
    author: "Sunday Chukwu",
    img: "Sunday Chukwu",
    userName: "Sunny",
    question: "How Do You Use WHILE….WEND Loop?",
    tags: ["loop", "Angular"],
    views: 128,
    answers: 0,
    timeAsked: 18,
    isAnswered: false,
  },

  {
    id: 6,
    author: "Phil Foden",
    img: "Phil Foden",
    userName: "Philly",
    question: "How to install software or upgrade from an old unsupported",
    tags: ["Software", "Prog"],
    views: 29,
    answers: 3,
    timeAsked: 19,
    isAnswered: true,
  },

  {
    id: 7,
    author: "Adeboye Afeez",
    img: "Adeboye Afeez",
    userName: "Heyzed",
    question: "What Is the Use of Relational and Arithmetic Operators?",
    tags: ["React", "Javascript"],
    views: 63,
    answers: 11,
    timeAsked: 20,
    isAnswered: true,
  },

  {
    id: 8,
    author: "Abdullahi Hadiza",
    img: "Abdullahi Hadiza",
    userName: "Ziza",
    question: "What Do You Mean by Low-Level Programming Language",
    tags: ["Prog", "Coding"],
    views: 18,
    answers: 0,
    timeAsked: 22,
    isAnswered: false,
  },

  {
    id: 9,
    author: "Michael Binuyo",
    img: "Michael Binuyo",
    userName: "Mickkystonz",
    question:
      "How do I Code in 32-Bit x86 Machine Code To Calculate the Nth Fibonacci Number.",
    tags: ["Fibonacci", "Code"],
    views: 38,
    answers: 0,
    timeAsked: 23,
    isAnswered: false,
  },

  {
    id: 10,
    author: "Jidechi Uzondu",
    img: "Jidechi Uzondu",
    userName: "Uzzy",
    question:
      "Must program be loaded into memory (RAM) before execution of the program.",
    tags: ["Program", "Code", "RAM"],
    views: 68,
    answers: 15,
    timeAsked: 23,
    isAnswered: true,
  },

  {
    id: 11,
    author: "Makumo David",
    img: "Makumo David",
    userName: "Makky",
    question: "Do command require a preceding line number.",
    tags: ["Program", "JS"],
    views: 149,
    answers: 0,
    timeAsked: 23,
    isAnswered: false,
  },

  {
    id: 12,
    author: "Olalekan Olamide",
    img: "Olalekan Olamide",
    userName: "Olammy",
    question: "Do command require a preceding line number.",
    tags: ["Program", "JS"],
    views: 2,
    answers: 0,
    timeAsked: 23,
    isAnswered: false,
  },

  {
    id: 13,
    author: "Adamu Musa",
    img: "Adamu Musa",
    userName: "adad",
    question: "How are string variables used in python and new lang Carbon.",
    tags: ["Python", "Carbon"],
    views: 81,
    answers: 44,
    timeAsked: 23,
    isAnswered: true,
  },

  {
    id: 14,
    author: "Davido Ifeanyi",
    img: "Davido Ifeanyi",
    userName: "Iffy",
    question: "How is division by zero undefined?",
    tags: ["Prog", "Javascript"],
    views: 50,
    answers: 13,
    timeAsked: 14,
    isAnswered: true,
  },

  {
    id: 15,
    author: "Chris Brown",
    img: "Chris Brown",
    userName: "Brish",
    question:
      "Can assignment operator be used to storea value, string or a computational result in a variable?",
    tags: ["Operator", "NextJS"],
    views: 2,
    answers: 0,
    timeAsked: 18,
    isAnswered: false,
  },

  {
    id: 16,
    author: "Recce James",
    img: "Recce James",
    userName: "Ece",
    question:
      "How can logical operator allow us to combine complex conditions?",
    tags: ["Software", "C#"],
    views: 194,
    answers: 78,
    timeAsked: 19,
    isAnswered: true,
  },

  {
    id: 17,
    author: "Olumide Hepzibah",
    img: "Olumide Hepzibah",
    userName: "Swaz",
    question:
      "A beta version of a software is different from an alpha version, why?",
    tags: ["Beta", "Software"],
    views: 39,
    answers: 27,
    timeAsked: 20,
    isAnswered: true,
  },

  {
    id: 18,
    author: "Ugheli Chika",
    img: "Ugheli Chika",
    userName: "Tahechi",
    question: "Do we really need software testing, and why?",
    tags: ["TSoftware", "Testing"],
    views: 3,
    answers: 0,
    timeAsked: 22,
    isAnswered: false,
  },

  {
    id: 19,
    author: "Pedri Gonzalez",
    img: "Pedri Gonzalez",
    userName: "Perry",
    question: "Is A++, A+, ACC, ALF, and APL programming languages",
    tags: ["Prog", "Lang"],
    views: 38,
    answers: 0,
    timeAsked: 23,
    isAnswered: false,
  },

  {
    id: 20,
    author: "Michael Dell",
    img: "Michael Dell",
    userName: "Miky",
    question: "What do we call the binary form of a target language?.",
    tags: ["Binary", "Code"],
    views: 192,
    answers: 74,
    timeAsked: 23,
    isAnswered: false,
  },

  {
    id: 21,
    author: "Daniel Akinbo",
    img: "Daniel Akinbo",
    userName: "Arakinrin",
    question:
      "Data structure is too hard for me, is it really needed in software engineering.",
    tags: ["Program", "JS"],
    views: 368,
    answers: 184,
    timeAsked: 23,
    isAnswered: true,
  },

  {
    id: 22,
    author: "Adam Sandler",
    img: "Adam Sandler",
    userName: "Sandy",
    question: "Where exactly should we use stack and array and why?",
    tags: ["Program", "JS", "Arrray"],
    views: 43,
    answers: 0,
    timeAsked: 23,
    isAnswered: false,
  },

  {
    id: 23,
    author: "Jumoke Babajide",
    img: "Jumoke Babajide",
    userName: "Jummy",
    question:
      "What are key differences between linear and non-linear data structure?",
    tags: ["DSA", "Algorithm"],
    views: 589,
    answers: 69,
    timeAsked: 23,
    isAnswered: true,
  },

  {
    id: 24,
    author: "Unago C. Shege",
    img: "Unago C. Shege",
    userName: "Sapa",
    question: "What are the concepts introduced in OOPs needed.",
    tags: ["OOP", "Object", "Class"],
    views: 7,
    answers: 0,
    timeAsked: 23,
    isAnswered: false,
  },
];

export const questionsUnanswered = [
  {
    id: 0,
    author: "Nweke Chidi",
    img: "Nweke Chidi",
    userName: "Chigoddy",
    question: "Fetch data using axios is so different from using fetch",
    tags: ["html", "css"],
    views: 5,
    answers: 0,
    timeAsked: 2,
    isAnswered: false,
  },

  {
    id: 2,
    author: "Michael Binuyo",
    img: "Michael Binuyo",
    userName: "Mickkystonz",
    question:
      "How to validate email using regex in javascript, s this trully possible",
    tags: ["regex", "python"],
    views: 38,
    answers: 0,
    timeAsked: 5,
    isAnswered: false,
  },

  {
    id: 5,
    author: "Sunday Chukwu",
    img: "Sunday Chukwu",
    userName: "Sunny",
    question: "How Do You Use WHILE….WEND Loop?",
    tags: ["loop", "Angular", "Go", "python"],
    views: 128,
    answers: 0,
    timeAsked: 18,
    isAnswered: false,
  },

  {
    id: 8,
    author: "Abdullahi Hadiza",
    img: "Abdullahi Hadiza",
    userName: "Ziza",
    question: "What Do You Mean by Low-Level Programming Language",
    tags: ["Prog", "Coding"],
    views: 18,
    answers: 0,
    timeAsked: 22,
    isAnswered: false,
  },

  {
    id: 9,
    author: "Michael Binuyo",
    img: "Michael Binuyo",
    userName: "Mickkystonz",
    question:
      "How do I Code in 32-Bit x86 Machine Code To Calculate the Nth Fibonacci Number.",
    tags: ["Fibonacci", "Code"],
    views: 38,
    answers: 0,
    timeAsked: 23,
    isAnswered: false,
  },

  {
    id: 11,
    author: "Makumo David",
    img: "Makumo David",
    userName: "Makky",
    question: "Do command require a preceding line number.",
    tags: ["Program", "JS"],
    views: 149,
    answers: 0,
    timeAsked: 23,
    isAnswered: false,
  },

  {
    id: 12,
    author: "Olalekan Olamide",
    img: "Olalekan Olamide",
    userName: "Olammy",
    question: "Do command require a preceding line number.",
    tags: ["Program", "JS"],
    views: 2,
    answers: 0,
    timeAsked: 23,
    isAnswered: false,
  },

  {
    id: 15,
    author: "Chris Brown",
    img: "Chris Brown",
    userName: "Brish",
    question:
      "Can assignment operator be used to storea value, string or a computational result in a variable?",
    tags: ["Operator", "NextJS"],
    views: 2,
    answers: 0,
    timeAsked: 18,
    isAnswered: false,
  },

  {
    id: 18,
    author: "Ugheli Chika",
    img: "Ugheli Chika",
    userName: "Tahechi",
    question: "Do we really need software testing, and why?",
    tags: ["TSoftware", "Testing"],
    views: 3,
    answers: 0,
    timeAsked: 22,
    isAnswered: false,
  },

  {
    id: 22,
    author: "Adam Sandler",
    img: "Adam Sandler",
    userName: "Sandy",
    question: "Where exactly should we use stack and array and why?",
    tags: ["Program", "JS", "Arrray"],
    views: 43,
    answers: 0,
    timeAsked: 23,
    isAnswered: false,
  },

  {
    id: 24,
    author: "Unago C. Shege",
    img: "Unago C. Shege",
    userName: "Sapa",
    question: "What are the concepts introduced in OOPs needed.",
    tags: ["OOP", "Object", "Class"],
    views: 7,
    answers: 0,
    timeAsked: 23,
    isAnswered: false,
  },
];

export const questionsAnswered = [
  {
    id: 1,
    author: "Bolanle Duke",
    img: "Bolanle Duke",
    userName: "Brandy",
    question:
      "How To Align Text Vertically Center Beside An Image In React Native With Code or can it be done any other way i really want you to help me out",
    tags: ["React", "Javascript"],
    views: 50,
    answers: 13,
    timeAsked: 5,
    isAnswered: true,
  },

  {
    id: 3,
    author: "Temitope Hamzat",
    img: "Temitope Hamzat",
    userName: "CodeT",
    question:
      "What is a potential pitfall with using typeof bar === 'object' to determine if bar is an object? How can this pitfall be avoided?",
    tags: ["html", "Javascript"],
    views: 13,
    answers: 10,
    timeAsked: 12,
    isAnswered: true,
  },

  {
    id: 4,
    author: "Adaeze Ndupu",
    img: "Adaeze Ndupu",
    userName: "Vermilion",
    question:
      "What is the significance, and what are the benefits, of including 'use strict' at the beginning of a JavaScript source file?",
    tags: ["Vue", "Javascript"],
    views: 50,
    answers: 13,
    timeAsked: 14,
    isAnswered: true,
  },

  {
    id: 6,
    author: "Phil Foden",
    img: "Phil Foden",
    userName: "Philly",
    question: "How to install software or upgrade from an old unsupported",
    tags: ["Software", "Prog"],
    views: 29,
    answers: 3,
    timeAsked: 19,
    isAnswered: true,
  },

  {
    id: 7,
    author: "Adeboye Afeez",
    img: "Adeboye Afeez",
    userName: "Heyzed",
    question: "What Is the Use of Relational and Arithmetic Operators?",
    tags: ["React", "Javascript"],
    views: 63,
    answers: 11,
    timeAsked: 20,
    isAnswered: true,
  },

  {
    id: 10,
    author: "Jidechi Uzondu",
    img: "Jidechi Uzondu",
    userName: "Uzzy",
    question:
      "Must program be loaded into memory (RAM) before execution of the program.",
    tags: ["Program", "Code", "RAM"],
    views: 68,
    answers: 15,
    timeAsked: 23,
    isAnswered: true,
  },

  {
    id: 13,
    author: "Adamu Musa",
    img: "Adamu Musa",
    userName: "adad",
    question: "How are string variables used in python and new lang Carbon.",
    tags: ["Python", "Carbon"],
    views: 81,
    answers: 44,
    timeAsked: 23,
    isAnswered: true,
  },

  {
    id: 14,
    author: "Davido Ifeanyi",
    img: "Davido Ifeanyi",
    userName: "Iffy",
    question: "How is division by zero undefined?",
    tags: ["Prog", "Javascript"],
    views: 50,
    answers: 13,
    timeAsked: 14,
    isAnswered: true,
  },

  {
    id: 16,
    author: "Recce James",
    img: "Recce James",
    userName: "Ece",
    question:
      "How can logical operator allow us to combine complex conditions?",
    tags: ["Software", "C#"],
    views: 194,
    answers: 78,
    timeAsked: 19,
    isAnswered: true,
  },

  {
    id: 17,
    author: "Olumide Hepzibah",
    img: "Olumide Hepzibah",
    userName: "Swaz",
    question:
      "A beta version of a software is different from an alpha version, why?",
    tags: ["Beta", "Software"],
    views: 39,
    answers: 27,
    timeAsked: 20,
    isAnswered: true,
  },

  {
    id: 20,
    author: "Michael Dell",
    img: "Michael Dell",
    userName: "Miky",
    question: "What do we call the binary form of a target language?.",
    tags: ["Binary", "Code"],
    views: 192,
    answers: 74,
    timeAsked: 23,
    isAnswered: false,
  },

  {
    id: 21,
    author: "Daniel Akinbo",
    img: "Daniel Akinbo",
    userName: "Arakinrin",
    question:
      "Data structure is too hard for me, is it really needed in software engineering.",
    tags: ["Program", "JS"],
    views: 368,
    answers: 184,
    timeAsked: 23,
    isAnswered: true,
  },

  {
    id: 23,
    author: "Jumoke Babajide",
    img: "Jumoke Babajide",
    userName: "Jummy",
    question:
      "What are key differences between linear and non-linear data structure?",
    tags: ["DSA", "Algorithm"],
    views: 589,
    answers: 69,
    timeAsked: 23,
    isAnswered: true,
  },
];
